
  [
    {
      "name": "The Dark Foyer",
    "description": "A dimly lit room that is deafening in sound with a single door at the end of the room...",
    "isSolved": false,
    "level": 1,
    "puzzle": [
      {
        "type": "riddle",
        "id": 1,
        "question": "What type of key opens a haunted house?",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "answer": "a spoo-key",
        "category": "house",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "KEY"
      },
      {
        "type": "riddle",
        "id": 2,
        "question": "A zombie, mummy, and a skeleton bought a house together. It had all the usual rooms except for one. Which one?",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "answer": "a living room",
        "category": "house",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "riddle",
        "id": 3,
        "question": "I have no body, head, or face, but I zoom from place to place. I haunt halls when night is near. What am I?",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": "a ghost",
        "category": "monsters",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "KEY"
      },
      {
        "type": "riddle",
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is made, bought, and used without the maker wanting it, the buyer needing it, or the user knowing it?",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": "a coffin",
        "category": "objects",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "riddle",
        "id": 5,
        "question": "I hang around a doorway and creak when people pass, at night I swing and scare the brave. What am I? ",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "answer": "a creaky door",
        "category": "objects",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "KEY"
      },
      {
        "type": "riddle",
        "id": 6,
        "question": "I have many teeth but I never bite, in a haunted house I chatter in the night. What am I?",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "answer": "a skeleton",
        "category": "monsters",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Hall of Doors",
    "description": "A long hallway of doors, but only two lead forward...",
    "isSolved": false,
    "level": 2,
    "puzzle": [
      {
        "type": "door",
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Choose the correct door (1-3).",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "numDoors": 3,
        "correctDoor": 2,
        "attempts": 0,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "door",
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Choose the correct door (1-5).",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "numDoors": 5,
        "correctDoor": 4,
        "attempts": 0,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "",
        "locked": true
      },
      {
        "type": "door",
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Choose the correct door (1-10).",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "numDoors": 10,
        "correctDoor": 7,
        "attempts": 0,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "door",
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Choose the correct door (1-15).",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "numDoors": 15,
        "correctDoor": 11,
        "attempts": 0,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "",
        "locked": true
      },
      {
        "type": "door",
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Choose the correct door (1-30).",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "numDoors": 30,
        "correctDoor": 3,
        "attempts": 0,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "door",
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Choose the correct door (1-40).",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "numDoors": 40,
        "correctDoor": 25,
        "attempts": 0,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "",
        "locked": true
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Cursed Room",
    "description": "A lone candles burns... though no one's been there for years",
    "isSolved": false,
    "level": 3,
    "puzzle": [
      {
        "type": "math",
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Solve: 8 * 12",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "equation": "8 * 12",
        "answer": 96,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "math",
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Solve: 44 * 10",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "equation": "44*10",
        "answer": 440,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "DOLL"
      },
      {
        "type": "math",
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Solve: 100 * 6 / 5",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "equation": "100*6/5",
        "answer": 120,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "math",
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Solve: 16 * 13",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "equation": "16*13",
        "answer": 208,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "DOLL"
      },
      {
        "type": "math",
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Solve: 14 * 27 / 9",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "equation": "14*27/9",
        "answer": 42,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "math",
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Solve: 124 * 9 / 18",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "equation": "124*9/18",
        "answer": 71,
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "DOLL"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "name": "Alchemy Lab",
    "description": "Strange fumes rise from bubbling bottles",
    "isSolved": false,
    "level": 4,
    "puzzle": [
      {
        "type": "trivia",
        "id": 19,
        "question": "In legends, which creature might guard an alchemist's secret potions?",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "category": "creatures",
        "answer": "a homunculus",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "POTION"
      },
      {
        "type": "trivia",
        "id": 20,
        "question": "What would a haunted cauldron most likely brew on its own at midnight?",
        "difficulty": "EASY",
        "category": "potions",
        "answer": "trouble",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "trivia",
        "id": 21,
        "question": "If a glowing green bottle starts humming, what's trapped inside?",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "category": "creatures",
        "answer": "a spirit",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "POTION"
      },
      {
        "type": "trivia",
        "id": 22,
        "question": "What ghostly gas might an alchemist accidentally create while mixing strange brews in the dark?",
        "difficulty": "MEDIUM",
        "category": "potions",
        "answer": "phosphorus vapors",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      },
      {
        "type": "trivia",
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Which element's symbol, Hg, comes from the alchemical name 'quicksilver'?",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "category": "elements",
        "answer": "mercury",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": "POTION"
      },
      {
        "type": "trivia",
        "id": 24,
        "question": "Which alchemical element was linked to death, rebirth, and the color black?",
        "difficulty": "HARD",
        "category": "elements",
        "answer": "lead",
        "isSolved": false,
        "reward": ""
      }
    ]
  }
]
